Your business is running smoothly right where you are, but you've got a case, actually a lot of
cases for taking your business here, here, and of course, here.
In this step, we will show you exactly how much easier it is to register and add offers across the
world with the help of Amazon Global Selling.
First, visit the sell globally page in your existing account and create a selling account in the
region in which you'd like to sell.
Now, you can track and manage your business across all regions in one place.
Next, review which of your current offers you want to feature in the new marketplaces.
Amazon provides a number of tools to help you manage your offers across regions, including setting
prices and translating offers into the right language.
Congratulations!
You're one step closer to selling across the world with the help of Amazon Global Selling.